<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./es_adjust_tool.sh</path>
		<name>ES Centering &amp; Scaling Tool</name>
		<desc>Scaling and centering for cases in 
which these operations within the service menu
and CRT geometry tool do not produce a perfectly centered screen.		
See Script wiki page for more information</desc>
		<image>./images/es_adjust_tool-image.png</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20241006T193838</lastplayed>
		<gametime>23</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./GunCon2_Calibration.sh</path>
		<name>GunCon2 Calibration</name>
		<desc>GunCon2 Calibration How To

You only need to do a first calibration once

* Start the calibration by pressing the gun trigger.
* Follow the onscreen instructions and aim at all the 4 circles with the cross in the middle.
* Try to be as exact as possible.
* The result will not be perfect even if you aimed exactly in the middle using the GunCon2's crosshair.
* This is normal..
			  
* Exit the script and save the settings by pressing A or B</desc>
		<image>./images/GunCon2_Calibration-image.png</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<playcount>23</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20241006T194141</lastplayed>
		<gametime>453</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./geometry.sh</path>
		<name>CRT Geometry Adjustments</name>
		<desc>Adjust CRT Geometry System Wide.
With this utility you can create a custom monitor if the standard ones show the image off-center.
Just follow the onscreen instructions to center grid using keyboard or gamepad.
Next you need to adjust Emulationstation using the ES Centering &amp; Scaling Tool.</desc>
		<image>./images/geometry-image.png</image>
		<manual>./manuals/CRT.sh-manual.pdf</manual>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20241031T124318</lastplayed>
		<gametime>564</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./grid_tool.sh</path>
		<name>CRT Grid Tool</name>
		<desc>The grid tool helps adjust image geometry using the CRT service menu.
Only when you’ve made the best possible adjustments with the grid tool should you use the geometry tool.
Always write down your default service menu values, save them on your phone, stick a note on the back of your TV,
or keep them somewhere safe. Just don’t lose them. Preserving these values gives you more CRT range adjustments.
If you push the CRT range too far in the geometry tool, you’ll have limited options for in-game adjustments later.</desc>
		<image>./images/grid_tool-image.png</image>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20241031T123400</lastplayed>
		<gametime>560</gametime>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
</gameList>
